BU Records: President Emeritus' Office (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1857-1995, undated, Bulk: 1985-1995
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
BU Records: President Emeritus' Office (Abner Vernon McCall)
Inclusive: 1857-1995, undated, Bulk: 1985-1995
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
BU/297
McCall, Abner Vernon, 1915-
40 document boxes
BU Records: President Emeritus' Office (Abner Vernon McCall) contains records relating to Judge Abner Vernon McCall's time as President Emeritus of Baylor University from 1985-1995. Records include correspondence, reports, and documents concerning Baylor University as well as external organizations McCall had involvement in.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
Abner Vernon McCall was born on 1915 June 9 in Perrin, Texas, to parents Gertrude Elizabeth Rhoades McCall and Harry Vernon McCall. At the age of 3, McCall’s father passed away from the flu. After his death, his mother was unable to care for McCall and his siblings, and they were placed in the Masonic School and Home in Fort Worth, Texas. Although not much is known about Abner’s early life at this school, it is well known that Abner flourished academically. Graduating as the Valedictorian of his class, Abner earned the prestigious Masonic Scholarship, providing him the funding to attend Baylor University. Continuing his successes at Baylor, McCall graduated as valedictorian of the Baylor Law Class of 1938.
Entering law practice, McCall remained near Baylor to teach law classes, serving as an assistant professor from 1938 to 1942. He left Baylor for one year to earn a Masters of Law at the University of Michigan. After receiving his degree, he worked with the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) for three years before returning to Baylor. Two years after his return, he was appointed Dean of the Law School. During his time teaching, he also was appointed a Texas Supreme Court Justice in 1956 June by then Governor Allan Shivers.
By 1959, McCall was appointed Executive Vice President of Baylor University. In 1961, McCall was appointed President of Baylor University, a position he held for 21 years. During his tenure at Baylor, he was instrumental in expanding Baylor’s campus, raising the enrollment numbers, and improving the financial conditions of the university. While McCall was president, he continued to teach law courses. In 1981, McCall became the Chancellor of Baylor. He served in this capacity until 1985, then served as President Emeritus.
McCall was known for his traditional Baptist views on social issues pertaining to campus life, including dancing, alcohol, and card playing. He served in many religious organizations in a variety of capacities, including President of the Baptist General Convention of Texas in 1964-1965 and Vice President of the Southern Baptist Convention in 1979-1980. Growing up surrounded by Masons, McCall was also involved in the Masonic Order and was coronated a 33rd degree Scottish Rite Mason in 1969. In 1991, McCall was honored with the Grand Cross, the highest honor granted to a Free Mason.
McCall passed away at the age of 90 on 1995 June 11 and is buried in Oakwood Cemetery in Waco, Texas.
Scope and Content
This collection begins in 1857 and ends in 1995, with some items undated. While this collection mainly encompasses files from Abner McCall's time as President Emeritus at Baylor University from June 1985 to 1995, some folders include materials from McCall's time as President and Chancellor.
Series I. Internal includes correspondence, reports, and other materials that were produced specifically by Baylor University. This includes departments, organizations, and correspondence topically related to events or issues at Baylor. Series II. External, the largest series, includes correspondence, reports, newsletters, and other materials that were produced outside of Baylor or for institutions outside of Baylor. This includes organizations such as the Baylor College of Medicine, Brazos Higher Education Authority, Cooper Foundation, Texas Scottish Rite Hospital, Texas System of Natural Laboratories, and many others. Some of these materials are related to McCall and his involvement in external organizations while others deal specifically with his position at Baylor. Series III. People includes correspondence and documents that were organized and filed by a person's last name. Series IV. Personal includes appointment books, personal correspondence, and speeches McCall wrote.
Arrangement
Prior to current processing, this collection was housed in labeled folders in no particular order. Original titles were retained where possible and any title information added during processing is noted in brackets in the folder titles.
Currently, the collection is organized in four series: I. Internal, II. External, III. People, IV. Personal. Within all five series, folders are arranged relatively alphabetically and chronological thereafter.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. BU/297. Acquired 1991-00-00
Related Resources
Items in related collections
BU Records: Chancellor's Office (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1980-1988, undated, Bulk: 1981-1985
BU Records: College of Medicine
BU Records: President's Office: Herbert Hal Reynolds
BU Records: Office of the President (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1845-1981, undated, Bulk: 1961-1981
Related references
“Abner Vernon McCall (1915-1995).”Abner Vernon McCall, The University of Texas at Austin. Accessed 2019 December 1.
Find A Grave, Inc. "Abner Vernon McCall." Memorial #15715101. Databases. Accessed 2019 December 1.
Saxon, Wolfgang. “Abner V. McCall, 80, Educator Who Led in Expansion of Baylor.” The New York Times, 1995 June 12.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
McCall, Abner, 1915-
Subjects (Organizations)
Baylor University -- Administration.; Baylor University -- History -- 20th century.; Baylor University -- Records and correspondence.; Baylor University. College of Medicine -- History.
Subjects
Baptist universities and colleges -- Texas -- Waco.
Genres
Appointment Books.; Business correspondence.; Minutes (Records); Newsletters.; Personal correspondence.; Records (Documents); Speeches.
- Internal, 1857-1995; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  This series includes correspondence, reports, minutes, and other materials relating to the inner-workings of Baylor. Materials produced specifically for Baylor or by Baylor departments, organizations, and individuals can be found in this series. Some files are restricted due to the existence of personally identifiable information, or based on the current restriction policy governing university archives. This series is in average condition.
  - Abner V. and Mary W. McCall Scholarship Fund, 1974-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Admissions, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Association (1 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Association (2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Association (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Association (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Association (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Association (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Association (1 of 4), 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Association (2 of 4), 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Association (3 of 4), 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Association (4 of 4), 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Association (1 of 6), 1990-1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Association (2 of 6), 1990-1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Association (3 of 6), 1990-1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Association (4 of 6), 1990-1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Association (5 of 6), 1990-1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Association (6 of 6), 1990-1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Association — Benefactors Life Insurance (1 of 3), 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Association — Benefactors Life Insurance (2 of 3), 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Association — Benefactors Life Insurance (3 of 3), 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Scholarship, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Baylor Funds (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1990-1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Baylor Funds (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1990-1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes (1 of 3), 1984-1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes (2 of 3), 1984-1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes (3 of 3), 1984-1993 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Budget Comparison Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Center for Private Enterprise, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Crouch Gift, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - External Affairs, 1985-1989 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Senate, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Gifts [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Governor Bill and Vara Daniel Historic Village, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Heritage Club, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Law School (1 of 2), 1985-1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Law School (2 of 2), 1985-1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Law School - History, 1857-1995 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Leadership and Vision, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Presidential Search, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Retired Professors Center, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Scholarships, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Strategic Planning Document Draft, 1985 November (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Student Foundation, 1985-1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- External, 1985-1995; 2
  This series includes correspondence, reports, minutes, publications, programs, and other materials relating to institutions and organizations outside of Baylor University. Some materials are related to McCall as an individual and his interests and affiliations, while others are directly related to his position as Chancellor. This series is in good condition.
  - Adopt-A-School (1 of 5), 1986-1993 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Adopt-A-School (2 of 5), 1986-1993 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Adopt-A-School (3 of 5), 1986-1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Adopt-A-School (4 of 5), 1986-1993 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Adopt-A-School (5 of 5), 1986-1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Anti-Crime Council of Texas (ACT), 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Anti-Crime Council of Texas (ACT), 1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Baptist Children’s Home, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Baptist Laity Journal, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Baptist General Convention (1 of 2), 1985-1990 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Baptist General Convention (2 of 2), 1985-1990 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1991-1995 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Baptist Joint Committee on Public Affairs, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Baptist Joint Committee/Religious Liberty Council, 1986-1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Baylor College of Medicine (1 of 2), 1985-1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Baylor College of Medicine (2 of 2), 1985-1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Baylor College of Medicine (1 of 2), 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Baylor College of Medicine (2 of 2), 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Baylor College of Medicine Board of Trustees, 1988 January 27 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Baylor College of Medicine Board of Trustees, 1988 March 16 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Baylor College of Medicine Board of Trustees, 1989 January 18 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Baylor College of Medicine Board of Trustees, 1990 July 18 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Baylor College of Medicine Board of Trustees, 1991 March 27 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Baylor College of Medicine Board of Trustees, 1991 July 24 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Baylor College of Medicine Board of Trustees, 1992 July 22 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Baylor College of Medicine Board of Trustees, 1993 November 17 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Baylor College of Medicine Board of Trustees, 1994 July 27 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Baylor College of Medicine Board of Trustees, 1995 January 25 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Baylor College of Medicine Board of Trustees Annual Meeting, 1995 May 24 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Baylor College of Medicine Board of Trustees Annual Meeting - Addendum, 1995 May 24 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Baylor College of Medicine Five-Year Report, 1989-1994 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Baylor College of Medicine Oral History Project, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Baylor Medical Center, 1993-1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Baylor Medical Foundation, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Baylor Medical Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Baylor Medical Foundation (1 of 2), 1985-1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Baylor Medical Foundation (2 of 2), 1985-1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Benefactors Life Insurance Company, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - The Brazos Club, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (1 of 15), 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (2 of 15), 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (3 of 15), 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (4 of 15), 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (5 of 15), 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (6 of 15), 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (7 of 15), 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (8 of 15), 1985-1988 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (9 of 15), 1985-1988 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (10 of 15), 1985-1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (11 of 15), 1985-1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (12 of 15), 1985-1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (13 of 15), 1985-1988 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (14 of 15), 1985-1988 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (15 of 15), 1985-1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (1 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (2 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (3 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (4 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (5 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (6 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (7 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (8 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (9 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (10 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (11 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (12 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (13 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (14 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (15 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (16 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (17 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, Inc. (18 of 18), 1989-1995 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Citizen National Republic Bank, 1985-1988 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Chamber of Commerce Education Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Cooper Foundation (1 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Cooper Foundation (2 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Cooper Foundation (3 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Cooper Foundation (4 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Cooper Foundation (5 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Cooper Foundation (6 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Cooper Foundation (7 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Cooper Foundation (8 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Cooper Foundation (9 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Cooper Foundation (10 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Cooper Foundation (11 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Cooper Foundation (12 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Cooper Foundation (13 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Cooper Foundation (14 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Cooper Foundation (15 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Cooper Foundation (16 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Cooper Foundation (17 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Cooper Foundation (18 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Cooper Foundation (19 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Cooper Foundation (20 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Cooper Foundation (21 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Cooper Foundation (22 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Cooper Foundation (23 of 23), 1985-1995 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Crime Commission (1 of 3), 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Crime Commission (2 of 3), 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Crime Commission (3 of 3), 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Dow Chemical Co. And Shell Oil Co. V. Domingon Castro Alfaro (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Dow Chemical Co. And Shell Oil Co. V. Domingon Castro Alfaro (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Pepper Museum Grant Proposal, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Education Commission of the States (1 of 3), 1985-1991 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Education Commission of the States (2 of 3), 1985-1991 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Education Commission of the States (3 of 3), 1985-1991 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - “The Economic Impact of Baylor College of Medicine and related programs on Harris County and Texas,” A Study Submitted to Baylor College of Medicine by M. Ray Perryman Consultants, Inc., 1988 November 8 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - First Federal Savings and Loan, 1986-1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - The Foundation Endowment Conference, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Freemasonry, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Greater Waco Chamber of Commerce, 1985-1988 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Horatio Alger Association (1 of 2), 1987-1992 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Horatio Alger Association (2 of 2), 1987-1992 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Horatio Alger Association (1 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Horatio Alger Association (2 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - The Institute for the Humanities at Salado, 1986-1988 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Kilgore Inn Project, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Leon Jaworski Foundation (1 of 5), 1985-1995 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Leon Jaworski Foundation (2 of 5), 1985-1995 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Leon Jaworski Foundation (3 of 5), 1985-1995 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Leon Jaworski Foundation (4 of 5), 1985-1995 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Leon Jaworski Foundation (5 of 5), 1985-1995 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Masonic Home Independent School District, 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Masonic Home and School of Texas, 1985-1988 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Masons Grand Lodge (1 of 3), 1985-1987 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Mason Grand Lodge (2 of 3), 1985-1987 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Mason Grand Lodge (3 of 3), 1985-1987 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Masons — Grand Lodge, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Members of Congress, 1985-1989 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - The Philosophical Society of Texas, 1985-1989 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Paul Piper Enterprises, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Philosopher Club (Waco), 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Planning Commission — Christian Higher Education, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Right to Work Committee (1 of 2), 1985-1988 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Right to Work Committee (2 of 2), 1985-1988 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Scottish Rite (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Scottish Rite (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Scottish Rite, 1988-1991 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Southern Baptist Convention (1 of 3), 1985-1990 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Southern Baptist Convention (2 of 3), 1985-1990 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Southern Baptist Convention (3 of 3), 1985-1990 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - SBC Today, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - State Bar College, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - State Ethics Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Texans Who Care, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Texans Who Care, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Texas Colleges and Universities Coordinating Board, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Texas Higher Education Coordinating Board, 1989-1995 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (1 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (2 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (3 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (4 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (5 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (6 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (7 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (8 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (9 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (10 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (11 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (12 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (13 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (14 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (15 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (16 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (17 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (18 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (19 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital (20 of 20), 1988-1995 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital — 1989 Board of Trustees’ Reference Manual (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital — 1991 Board of Trustees’ Reference Manual (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital — 1992 Board of Trustees’ Reference Manual (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital — 1993 Board of Trustees’ Reference Manual (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital — 1995 Board of Trustees’ Reference Manual (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Texas Supreme Court (1 of 4), 1986-1988 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Texas Supreme Court (2 of 4), 1986-1988 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Texas Supreme Court (3 of 4), 1986-1988 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Texas Supreme Court (4 of 4), 1986-1988 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Texas Supreme Court Justice Committee, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (1 of 13), 1987-1995 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (2 of 13), 1987-1995 (Box 32, Folder 4)